Guide to the Consumer Reports. Audiovisual materials, 1940-2011 and undated RL.11802
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Public Relations and Publicity, 1961-2011; undated; 6
  - Corporate Events and Activities, 1961-2011; undated; 25
    - Press Conference on Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0975)
    - Press Conference Video Presentation, 1996 Aug. 13 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-105)
    - Press Conference Video Presentation, 1996 Aug. 20 (Box 59, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0044)
    - Product Planning Seminar, 1997 Mar. 24 (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0540)
    - Promo Reel, 1990 May 03 (Box 36, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-015)
    - Public eye with Bryant Gumbel, 1998 Aug. 26 (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0478)
    - Public Service Projects, 1996 May 09 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0073)
    - R&A on Web Site, 1998 June 10 (Box 99, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-240)
    - Rachel Ray (Edit), Undated (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-014)
    - Rachel Ray (RAW), Undated (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-004)
    - Reports Television Seminar, 1994 Mar. 31 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0079)
    - Road Trip '03, 2003 (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-008)
    - Satellite Media Tour Bob Knoll, 1998 Mar. 31 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0607)
    - Satellite Media Tour Bob Knoll, 1998 Mar. 31 (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0873)
    - Selling America's Kids press conference, 1990 (Box 138, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-248)
    - Seminar - Strategic Planning, 1997 Mar. 24 (Box 59, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0034)
    - Seminar (mid), 1994 June 08 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0078)
    - Seminar (MID), 1994 June 08 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0577)
    - Seminar Tapes, 1994 (Box 59, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0036)
    - Seminar: Advocacy Offices, 1993 July 29 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0556)
    - Seminar: Library, 1994 Apr. 27 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0077)
    - Seminar: Library, 1994 Apr. 27 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0581)
    - Seminar: Tech Division, 1993 Apr. 29 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0076)
    - Seminar: Tech Division, 1993 Apr. 30 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0579)
    - Seminar: Technical Division, 1993 Apr. 29 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0578)
    - Shots of Drivers Handling, 1999 Apr. 15 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-143)
    - Special Board Meeting, 1965 Mar. 13 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-050)
    - Staff Meeting, 1994 May 23 (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0543)
    - Staff Meeting, 1994 May 23 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0562)
    - Staff Meeting, 1994 May 23 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0568)
    - Staff Meeting, 1994 Oct. 17 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0025)
    - Staff Meeting, 1994 Oct. 17 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0567)
    - Staff Meeting, 1995 Feb. 06 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0024)
    - Staff Meeting, 1995 Feb. 06 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0566)
    - Staff Meeting, 1996 Oct. 15 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0565)
    - Staff Meeting Copy, 1995 Oct. 02 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0016)
    - Still, 2000 Sept. 28 (Box 27, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-052)
    - Stills, staff testimonials, 2000 Oct. 02 (Box 27, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-049)
    - Style Book, 2005 May 13 (Box 137, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-721)
    - Tape #3 Executive Session, 1972 July 22 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-002)
    - Tape #5 Alexandria, VA meeting, 1972 Oct. 06; 1972 Oct. 08 (Box 5, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-001)
    - Tape 1 Consumers Union Welcome Donato, 2001 Nov. 28 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-245)
    - Tape 2 Welcome to Consumers Union, 2003 Feb. 11 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-290)
    - Tape 2 Welcome to the Consumers Union, 2001 Dec. 06 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-233)
    - Tape 3, 2002 Feb. 11 (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-121)
    - Tech Seminar Shoe Testing, 1993 June 24 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0083)
    - Tech/Admin Seminar, 1995 Apr. 29 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0082)
    - Tech/Statistical Services, 1997 Oct. 08 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0051)
    - Test Inform Protect, 1993 Oct. (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0491)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0007)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0065)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0068)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 70, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0223)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0391)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0499)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0500)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0501)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0502)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0503)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0726)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0789)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 Apr. 05 (Box 105, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-378)
    - Test, Inform, Protect: Welcome to Consumers Union, 2010 Apr. 05 (Box 105, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-380)
    - Testing & Guest CRG012, 060, 030, & CRT012, 060, 030, 2002 Jan. 18 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0005)
    - Town Hall Meeting, 2001 May 24 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0588)
    - Town Hall MTG, 1996 Jan. 17 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0013)
    - Town Meeting, 1996 May 15 (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0534)
    - Town Meeting, 1996 May 15 (Box 59, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0049)
    - Town Meeting, 1997 Feb. 04 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0019)
    - Town Meeting, 1997 Oct. 22 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0571)
    - Town Meeting, 1997 Oct. 22 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0020)
    - Town Meeting, 1998 Feb. 02 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0026)
    - Town Meeting, 1998 May 26 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0589)
    - Town Meeting, 1998 Oct. 04 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0021)
    - Town Meeting, 1998 Oct. 14 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0552)
    - Town Meeting, 1999 Feb. 25 (Box 59, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0047)
    - Town Meeting, 1999 Feb. 25 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0564)
    - Town Meeting, 1999 Nov. 11 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0583)
    - Town Meeting, 2000 Feb. 01 (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0533)
    - Town Meeting, 2000 Oct. 11 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0561)
    - Town Meeting, 2000 Oct. 11 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0592)
    - Town Meeting, 2001 Jan. 29 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0587)
    - Town Meeting, 2001 Nov. 15 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0575)
    - Town Meeting, 2002 Mar. 25 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0549)
    - Town Meeting, 2002 Mar. 25 (Box 59, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0045)
    - Town Meeting, 2002 Mar. 25 (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0531)
    - Travel Press Conference, 2001 Sept. 21 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0665)
    - Visit of 42 College Instructors to Consumers Union, 1973 Jan. 01 (Box 71, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-003)
    - Web Site Seminar, 1996 Nov. 25 (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0547)
    - Welcome to Consumer Reports, Undated (Box 70, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0222)
    - Welcome to Consumer Reports/Consumers Union, 2003 May (Box 120, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-120)
    - Welcome to Consumer Reports/Consumers Union, 2003 May (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0584)
    - Welcome to Consumer Union, 2003 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0453)
    - Welcome to Consumer Union, 2003 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0454)
    - Welcome to Consumer Union, 2003 (Box 39, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-009)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union, 2001 Dec. (Box 84, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-132)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union, 2003 (Box 88, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-195)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union, 2003 (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0455)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union, 2003 (Box 60, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-125)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union, 2003 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0496)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union, 2003 (Box 84, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-131)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union, 2003 Apr. 04 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-231)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union, 2003 Apr. 04 (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0498)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union (Repeated loop), Undated (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0490)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union Elena & Julia tape 3, 2001 Nov. 28 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-250)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union John Seteja, 2001 Nov. 28 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-251)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union Julia tape 4, 2001 Nov. 28 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-246)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union Needs Some Supers, 2003 Mar. 25 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-014)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union Tape 3, 2001 Dec. 06 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-238)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union Tape 4, 2001 Dec. 06 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-239)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union, Consumers Need to Know, Suzuki Samurai, Undated (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0495)
    - Welcome to Consumers Union, Suzuki hi-lights, Consumers want to know, Undated (Box 84, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0487)
    - Welcome to the Consumer Union, 1966 Aug. 18 (Box 71, Film-reel RL11802-F16-195)
    - Welcome to the Consumer Union, 1993 Oct. 12 (Box 71, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-045)
    - Welcome to the Consumer Union, Undated (Box 82, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0166)
    - Welcome to the Consumer Union, Undated (Box 71, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-046)
    - Welcome to the Consumers Union, 2003 May (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1182)
    - Yonkers, 1999 June 02 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-133)
    - Yonkers, 1999 June 02 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-135)
    - Yonkers Conf. Table Shopper Warhouse, 1999 June 02 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-145)
    - Yonkers Control Room w/Emilio, 1999 June 01 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-141)
    - Yonkers Library and Ref, 1999 June 01 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-147)
    - Zabinski, 2000 Oct. 02 (Box 27, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-041)
  - Media Coverage, 1961-2010; undated; 26
    - 20/20, 2000 Feb. 18 (Box 106b, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1079)
    - 20/20 SUVS, 1997 Sept. 11 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0988)
    - A Conversation on Marketing--Marketing #8 Warne-Britt-Wright, 1966 June 27 (Box 2, Film-reel RL11802-F16-011)
    - A tour of Consumers Union Testing Facilities 1. Behind Closed Doors; CBS Early Show, 2002 Feb. 27; 2005 Dec. 19 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0002)
    - A Visit to Consumers Union, 1961 (Box 44, Film-reel RL11802-F16-152)
    - A Visit to Consumers Union, 1968 Dec. 13 (Box 5, Film-reel RL11802-F16-054)
    - A.H. Perlmutter Consumer Reports Dollars & Sense Protection Master, 1982 Sept. 23 (Box 28, Video-reel RL11802-vid1-002)
    - ABC Children First Health & Safety Basics, 1999 Feb. 16 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0955)
    - ABC News Clip, 2004 May 16 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0849)
    - ABC-GMA Round Up, Undated (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1120)
    - Andrea Scott Supermarkets, 1993 Aug. 24 (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0097)
    - Annie Leonard The story of Stuff, Undated (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-043)
    - Annual Board Meeting/Tribute to Betty Furness Part: 1, 1993 Oct. 16 (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-138)
    - Annual Board of Directors, 1984 Oct. 13 (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-174)
    - Annual Board of Directors meeting, 1974 Oct. (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-178)
    - Annual Board of Directors meeting, 1985 Oct. 19 (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-175)
    - Annual Board of Directors meeting, 1987 Oct. 17 (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-176)
    - Annual Board of Directors meeting, 1988 Oct. 15 (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-177)
    - Annual Meeting, 1964 Sept. 26 (Box 74, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-043)
    - Annual Meeting, 1980 Oct. 18 (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-163)
    - Annual Meeting, 1995 Oct. 14 (Box 123, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0591)
    - Annual Meeting, 2000 Oct. 21 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0032)
    - Annual Meeting, 2004 Oct. 16 (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0383)
    - Annual Meeting, 2008 Oct. 25 (Box 120, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-389)
    - Annual Meeting, Undated (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0031)
    - Annual Meeting, Undated (Box 59, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0046)
    - Annual Member Board Meeting, 1975 Oct. (Box 111, Video-reel RL11802-RR-179)
    - Arthur Stantz about Persia Campbell #253, 1980 Feb. 06 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-161)
    - Averell Hartman about Persia Campbell #254, 1980 Feb. 06 (Box 114, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-162)
    - Backovers Interview with David Champion, 2004 Jan. 01 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0797)
    - Barb Consumers Union Facilities, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0515)
    - Behind Closed Doors with Joan Lunden Show 29, 2002 Feb. 27 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0003)
    - Behind the Scenes at Consumer Reports Testing Labs The Early Show, 2005 Dec. 29 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0006)
    - Best Time to Buy, Mandy Walker, Consumer Reports Inside Edition, 2004 May 21 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0828)
    - Betty Furness Morning News, 1972 Sept. 25 (Box 65, Film-reel RL11802-F16-188)
    - Betty Furness TV piece about Consumers Union/CR, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-058)
    - B-Knoll c-span CBS This Morning, Undated (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0095)
    - Bob Edwards W/ Bob Knoll, 1995 (Box 85, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-195)
    - Bob Greene - Consumer Reports Challenge Oprah Winfrey, 2007 May 22 (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-018)
    - Bob Karpel Original, 2007 Dec. 07 (Box 58, Video-cassette RL11802-MDV-002)
    - Bob Knoll Live on CBS This Morning & CNN Morning News, 1997 Mar. 17 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0128)
    - Burdon Agatee at Hofstra Law School about Persia Campbell #244, Undated (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-149)
    - Business DWM & AML, 1962 Mar. 26-27 (Box 75, Audio-reel RL11802-RR-134)
    - Buyer's Bible Under Attack, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0976)
    - Buyer's Bible Under Attack, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0977)
    - Buyer's Bible Under Attack, 1999 Nov. 30 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0982)
    - CBS Evening News, 2003 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0684)
    - CBS Eye on People A Day in the Life, 1998 Apr. 03 (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0872)
    - CBS News, 1999 Oct. 16 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0646)
    - CBS This Morning, C-SPAN, FX Breakfast Time, CH. 7 Eyewitness News NY, Paige - New Cars, 1996 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0127)
    - Celebration Grand Central Terminal, Undated (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-331)
    - Change Makers the Struggle for Consumer Rights, 1995 (Box 85, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-375)
    - Channel 2 WCBS NYC Coverage of Post Chiron HC Speech Republican reaction 48 hrs Grease, 1993 Sept. 22 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0132)
    - Charlie Rose, 2000 May 18 (Box 106a, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1061)
    - Check 21 CNN, 2004 Sept. 06 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0733)
    - Child Safety Seat Story, 1995 July 26 (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0094)
    - Child Safety Seats, Press Briefing, Presentation, Undated (Box 61, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0062)
    - Choate Address, Undated (Box 80, Video-reel RL11802-vid2-004)
    - Choicepoint Software - World News Tonight ABC National, 2005 Mar. 02 (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0393)
    - CN8- Money Matters, 2005 Apr. 26 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0845)
    - CNBC Moye Thompson Toy Test Results; Elements on Today reports, 1995 Dec.; 1995 Nov. 21 (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0101)
    - CNBC The Money Club - New Cars Paige, 1996 Feb. 27 (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0220)
    - CNN, 2003 Dec. 29 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0793)
    - CNN, ???? Oct. 10 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0686)
    - CNN American Morning Mattresses, 2005 May 17 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0868)
    - CNN American Morning Mattresses, 2005 May 17 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0869)
    - CNN Madcow Interview Jean & Feed Industry Rep., 2003 June 11 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0765)
    - CNN Paul Sahn Show Blind Spots David Champion, 2005 Nov. 02 (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0386)
    - CNN Zillions, 1995 (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0213)
    - CNNFN Flipside Dangerous Supplements, 2004 Apr. 28 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0820)
    - CNNFN Your Money, 2004 Apr. 21 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1093)
    - CNN-Money line, 2000 Oct. 06 (Box 106, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1026)
    - Cocktail Hour #1, 2010 June 29 (Box 61, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-059)
    - Colbert Report, 2010 July 03; 08 (Box 70, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-338)
    - Connie Corbett, 1994 July 14 (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0099)
    - Connie Corbett on Good Morning America, 1994 July 14 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0140)
    - Consumer Brides Guide Segments on Today Show, 2002 July (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0774)
    - Consumer Movement #128274, Undated (Box 120, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-390)
    - Consumer Movement History #246, Undated (Box 115, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-151)
    - Consumer Reports 60 Minutes II, 2000 June 06 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1192)
    - Consumer Reports Lisa Lee Freeman TV Appearances, 2006 May 04; 2005 Mar. 31; 2005 Jan. 29; 2005 July 19 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1130)
    - Consumer Reports Mandy Walker TV Appearances; Jennifer Stockberger TV Appearances, 2006 Apr.; 2005 June; 2006 July; 2005 Oct. (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1134)
    - Consumer Reports Mention on Sabrina the Teenage Witch ABC Family, 2009 Feb. 21 (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-005)
    - Consumer Reports on Hollywood Squares CBS, 1998 Oct. 28 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0638)
    - Consumer Reports on TV, 2002 Oct. (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0778)
    - Consumer Reports on TV 2004 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0846)
    - Consumer Reports Oyster Awards, 2006 Mar. 24 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1104)
    - Consumer Reports The Call Main St Business, 2010 May 13 (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-013)
    - Consumer Reports The Call Main St Business, 2010 May 13 (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-015)
    - Consumer Reports TV Appearances: Amanda Walker, 2006 Apr.; 2005 June; 2006 July (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1133)
    - Consumer Reports tv Appearances: Jennifer Stockburger, 2005 Oct. (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0864)
    - Consumer Reports TV News Glass Table Alert, 2006 Mar. 05 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-010)
    - Consumer Reports visit by KFMB-TV San Diego, 1999 May (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0956)
    - Consumer Reports/Consumers Union, 2003 May (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-009)
    - Consumer Union 533 to 549, 1972 June 23 (Box 25, Film-reel RL11802-F16-117)
    - Consumer Union 533 to 549, 1972 June 23 (Box 25, Film-reel RL11802-F16-118)
    - Consumer Union Interview with: Rhoda Karpatkin, 1985 Nov. 21 (Box 64, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-143)
    - Consumers Union (Unreadable), Undated (Box 4, Film-reel RL11802-F16-026)
    - Consumers Union Clips, 2001 Nov.; 2001 Mar. (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-197)
    - Consumers Union Compilation of TV News Clips, 1998 June; 1998 July; 1998 Aug. (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0875)
    - Consumers Union on TV, 2002 Nov.; 2001 Jan. (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0676)
    - Consumers Union Short News Clips, 1998 June-Sept. (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0755)
    - Consumers Union TV Clips, 2001 Nov.; 2002 Mar. (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0904)
    - CRHPS Radio Spots, Undated (Box 85, Audio-cassette RL11802-CS-198)
    - CRMA Expert Laura Washington Your Money, 2004 Mar. 18 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0784)
    - C-Span RW Johnson, ???? Mar. 26 (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0218)
    - Dan Goleman on CBS This Morning Mind/Body, 1993 Feb. 22 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0133)
    - Dateline Ice Cream, 2002 June 09 (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0376)
    - Dateline NBC An Ounce of Prevention; The Food Chain, 1996 Apr. 02; 1997 Mar. 14 (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0536)
    - Dateline NBC Crib Sheets, 1998 Oct. 21 (Box 69, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0188)
    - David Ansley on State of Mind - America's Talking, Undated (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0090)
    - David Champion on 20/20, 2004 Mar. 22 (Box 108, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0862)
    - David Champion Satellite TV Tour, 2002 Mar. 27 (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0377)
    - David Champion Segment on Clayson/SUV Safety/Garner, 2002 Dec. 04 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1164)
    - David Champion World News Tonight with Peter Jennings, 2000 Sept. 12 (Box 106a, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1055)
    - David Champion, Peter Sawcheck, Ronnie Sandroff, Tom Mutchler, 2004 May 21; 2004 Sept. 28 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1114)
    - David Heim Appearances on WCBS and WNBC Evening Local News (NYC), 2004 Jan./Feb. (Box 106, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1018)
    - David Heim in House Party, 1990 Sept. 09 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0125)
    - David Heim on CNN, 1992 Apr. 04 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0609)
    - David Heim Today Show, 1995 (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0930)
    - David Heim Today Show, 1995 May 23 (Box 68, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0096)
    - David Pittle Hardball with Chris Matthews Segment on SUVs and the Recent Increase in Highway Traffic Fatalities; David Champion Segment on The Danger of Blind Sports Behind Vehicles, 2003 Apr. 28 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1205)
    - David Pittle Hardball with Chris Matthews Segment on SUVs and the Recent Increase in Highway Traffic Fatalities; David Champion Segment on The Danger of Blind Sports Behind Vehicles, 2003 Apr. 28 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1229)
    - Dean Gallea Computer Network, 2002 Aug. 06 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1163)
    - Dean Gallea CR July 2003 Walmart Computer, 2003 June 11 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0941)
    - Dean Gallea Talking about Windows XP, 2001 Oct. 24 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0657)
    - Deregulation Jim Guest #1, 2, 3 Rick Snyder Sharna Law, Undated (Box 119, Audio-cassette RL11802-VHS-0546)
    - Dialogo Con Glenis. Topico: Que es el Consumer Union?, 2001 Sept. 26 (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0723)
    - Discussion of Consumer Reports Auto Issue Cable Market, 2006 Mar. 6 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1097)
    - DIY Network Sweat Equity Episode DSEQ-106, Undated (Box 1, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-001)
    - DoBon WS Robert; Jeff Fox on WPIX, 1994 Sept. 16; 1994 Sept. 23 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0131)